So, welcome to one another video and in this we are going to discuss of the thing which
will be commonly used by the detectors to disable the antivirus software like Windows
Defender from the machine.
So, we are going to talk about one of the command and interface basically DISM deployment
image servicing management.
So this feature in Microsoft Windows is used to remove or modify the even more modify
the features from Microsoft service ok.
For an example if you want to add any new service or if you need to enable the service you
can use DASM based PowerShell command line to enable and disable services ok.
So, by using the legitimate DASM deployment image servicing management utility the threat
factors abusing the Microsoft Defender tool basically they will be turning off they will
be disabling the service ok.
So, let me give you the command line here so here you can find it is used to disable
the Microsoft Defender.
So, you this is the PowerShell command and so if you need to execute this command line the only
way you can choose is the PowerShell ok.
By the machine good hang let me show you in the primary machine.
So, if you execute this command line so your Defender will be get disabled ok.
So, because it was not disabled because I just have a bit of a defender it was combining
running with running with the reverse ok.
So, but if you use any kind of any any machine it will be it will be good to go ahead ok.
So, this is the easiest way and I was showing this command line to if you are doing
to forming some kind of a blue timing operation or 4 and 6 units to understand this is
the command line so used by the threat actors to disable the antivirus software and not
an antivirus software in those defender from the machine.
So, I hope this looks to be a good and we will jump on to the next video.
See you guys bye bye.